{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","address":"13700 Bringard","zipcode":"48205","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","licenseNumber":"035251","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/29/2016","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"210.0","geom":"0101000020E61000008C30861E03BF54C088EE8B7E06394540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44242","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","inspectionDate":"2018-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44242","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44242","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALL(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44242","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"44242","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"42585","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","inspectionDate":"2018-06-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42585","inspectionDate":"6/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41198","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","inspectionDate":"2018-01-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41198","inspectionDate":"1/9/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"STEAM TABLE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"41198","inspectionDate":"1/9/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"38941","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","inspectionDate":"2017-04-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38941","inspectionDate":"4/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"38941","inspectionDate":"4/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"inspectionid":"38941","inspectionDate":"4/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"36755","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","inspectionDate":"2016-09-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36755","inspectionDate":"9/26/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1165","name":"Trix Elementary","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1165"}}